{
    "id": "a13d177db8284901bed44019dfbb6d8a",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ....................... home now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26c018c7c5df4234bb741d63041d384a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would prefer to go in December ..................... in May.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "rather than",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "388ee2eea26f47548315183b59b90e3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer starting early rather than ....................... everything to the last minute.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "to leave",
                "leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d87e4ff01d344f299a5c385c7031f2c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer to walk ...................... drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "rather than",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6732868a80db4e6f8075c5a5e6fa685a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather you .................... in a hostel than in a hotel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stay",
                "stayed",
                "staying"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c3cb8e365bc7445088072c846f3435dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ........................ a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "found",
                "have found"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fef642dd501c4bd98eef47efc67f6b86"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ........................ face the enemy than surrender.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "would rather",
                "prefer"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "28d9fec58f284ed59c8be6b8dd98e7f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "They would rather build a new house .................... repair the old one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "than to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "870f6986a4214a738fae336ebb7e7036"
        },
        {
            "question": "We would rather you ......................... to bed now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4dab165ce2e54283b534b8dcb68d9bfd"
        },
        {
            "question": "We would rather you .................... the work yourself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "did",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fa13dc48875c471e8100960cf1bcfeee"
        }
    ]
}